Eric M. Sinovic

Email: ericsinovic@gmail.com
Website: https://esinovic.github.io/

Address: 111 Probandt #334 San Antonio, TX 78204

Phone: 402-270-4134

Personal Summary

I'm a full-stack software developer with a knowledge of a wide range of tools and development philosophies. I have a wide breadth of experience in designing creative digital solutions to problems presented, as well as being an effective member of any team. I have created several front-end applications as well as the associated business logic powering them for my team. Versatile as a result of having both back-end and front-end development experience, creative, experienced in design, and adept at client-developer interaction, I am motivated and capable of being an effective member of any software development team.

Education:

University of Nebraska - Lincoln Graduated: August 2016

Bachelor of Science GPA: 3.7

Majors: Computer Science, History, Classics **Minors:** Japanese, East Asian Studies

Experience:

Application Developer - Union Pacific Railroad

April 2018 - Present

- Tasked with leading development and design of two major capital projects.
- Designed the UX components for several programs used widely in the company.
- Managed a team of both on-shore and off-shore developers.
- Oversaw interactions with the customers regarding the projects I was leading, letting me take advantage of my communication skills.

Junior Application Developer Union Pacific Railroad

August 2016 - April 2018

Omaha, NE

- Built a variety of styles of software for the crew services including tools for data analysis, employee services, and automating crew dispatching tasks.
- Modernized several core applications from legacy architecture to current day standards
- Retained in the company through two downsizings and subsequently promoted.

Interface Developer

May 2014-August 2016

Nebraska Student Information Services

Lincoln, NE

- Created web applications focused on managing and interacting with databases of colleges throughout the state using a combination of HTML, JS, and Peoplecode.
- Trained in Oracle's Peoplesoft framework along with coding experience in Peoplecode.
- Created a series of reporting tools using Microsoft Report Builder.

Computer Skills:

·Java ·Javascript ·Angular ·UI/UX Design ·HTML/CSS ·React ·MySQL/PLSQL ·Git/TortiseSVN ·Web Development ·Database Design ·Agile Development